Previously on the show.
上集說到
The sheep thought Wolffy took
小羊們以為灰太狼拿走了
the green color pencil that was used for creating rainbows,
用來製造彩虹的綠顏色筆
so they tailed him secretly.
於是偷偷跟踪他
But they discovered that it was a misunderstanding.
最後卻發現是一場誤會
It turned out that the green color pencil was in Paddi's backpack all along.
原來綠顏色筆一直在懶羊羊的背包裡
So what will happen next?
那麼接下來會發生什麼呢？
"Flying Island: The Sky Adventure: Crisis of Doppelgangers."
《奇幻天空島之》
Paddi!
懶羊羊
Where did Paddi go this early in the morning?
懶羊羊一大早去哪了？
The early bird gets the worms.
早起的羊兒有果吃
Paddi, you are abusing Magic Train again.
懶羊羊，你又亂用嘻哈號了
Sorry, I won't do it again.
對不起，下次不亂用了
It's our turn to clean today.
今天輪到我們打掃衛生
Yes, I promise I will complete the task.
是，我保證完成任務
The current time is 12 noon...
現在時間12點整，12點整
Oh no! The limited sale of rainbow pudding has started.
糟了，彩虹布丁限量購買活動開始了
Wait. Didn't you say we're doing the cleaning together?
等等，不是說好了一起打掃衛生嗎？
I will use my doppelgangers to help you with the cleaning.
我用分身來幫你打掃啊
Oh no! I won't make it!
糟了，來不及了
Oh dear, it's Wolffy.
是灰太狼
How about I buy you this car?
爸爸買這輛小車給你怎麼樣啊？
You just bought me one yesterday.
你昨天才送了一輛給我
How about this one?
那這個呢？
You bought me that the day before yesterday too.
你前天也送了給我
Let's look at other toys.
那我們再看看別的吧
What other toys has Willie not played with before?
還有什麼玩具 是小灰灰沒有玩過的呢？
Oh, I can't think of anything.
想不到啊
I should leave before Wolffy finds out I'm here.
趁沒被灰太狼發現之前我趕快離開
No. I have to find a place to hide first.
不行，我得先找個地方躲起來
This is strange. Where did that little spaceship go?
奇怪，剛才的小飛船跑哪去了？
Dad, I want this spaceship.
爸爸…我要這艘小飛船
Shop owner, I'll take this.
老闆，我要這個
Sure.
好的
Great! Let's go home and play with the spaceship.
太好了，回家玩小飛船了
How did this happen?
怎麼會這樣？
I can finally work on my invention.
終於可以安心地發明了
Spaceship, go...
小飛船，開啊開
If I knew this would happen, I'd have cleaned with Weslie.
早知道這樣 還不如和喜羊羊一起打掃衛生呢
No. I must escape before Wolffy finds out.
不行 要在灰太狼發現之前逃出去才行
Great. The gate is open.
太好了，大門居然開著
Wow! The spaceship is moving on its own again.
太神奇了，小飛船又自己動了
This is strange. Did I get the recipe wrong?
奇怪，難道是配方弄錯了
I'm so close to escaping.
馬上就要成功逃脫了
Spaceship, why are you going around? Let's play together.
小飛船你怎麼到處亂跑？ 我們一起玩啊
How can I let Willie know I am here without letting Wolffy know?
有什麼辦法既讓小灰灰知道我 又不會驚動灰太狼呢？
This is...
這是…
It worked. Willie recognized me.
成功了，小灰灰認出我了
Dad. Look. This spaceship can stack blocks on its own.
爸爸…快來看 這艘小飛船能自己玩積木啊
Oh no! I can't let Wolffy find out.
糟了，不能讓灰太狼發現
Dad, look.
爸爸你看
This is strange.
奇怪
Willie, I'm really busy now. Go play on your own.
小灰灰，爸爸現在很忙 你自己先玩吧
Phew!
好險
This way, Willie will surely understand.
用這個方法小灰灰一定能明白
Willie, look this way.
小灰灰快看這邊
What did Willie draw?
小灰灰畫的是什麼呀？
Great! Wolffy left.
太好了，灰太狼走開了
Now I can tell Willie my identity openly.
現在可以光明正大地 告訴小灰灰我的身份了
Willie, look this way.
小灰灰，快往這邊看
Willie.
小灰灰
I give up.
我放棄了
Willie, come with me. We're going out.
小灰灰，來陪媽媽出去一下
Okay.
好
-Let's go. -Okay.
-我們走吧 -好
Good timing.
好機會
What was that sound?
剛才那是什麼聲音？
Wolffy almost found me again.
差點又被灰太狼發現了
What should I do now? Right!
現在怎麼辦呢？對了
I didn't think they could help out with cleaning too.
沒想到它們還會打掃衛生
Paddi!
懶羊羊
How come my doppelgangers are not here yet?
我的分身怎麼還不來？
This is strange. Where did the screw go?
奇怪，螺絲釘掉哪去了
Oh no! Wolffy is coming.
糟了，灰太狼來了
I still need a hammer and an apple.
還差一個鐵鎚，差個蘋果
I'm safe finally.
終於安全了
Thank you, Paddi.
謝謝你啊，懶羊羊
The goat I have wanted to catch is right by me after all.
原來我要對付的小羊就在我身邊啊
You are not getting away this time.
看你還怎麼逃
They're here at last.
終於來了
Since you are here, let me give you a taste of my vacuum cleaner
既然來了，就讓你體驗一下
that is specially designed to
我這個專門對付嘻哈號分體的強力…
deal with Magic Train's doppelgangers.
吸塵器
Wolffy, I'm afraid you'll be disappointed.
灰太狼，恐怕要讓你失望了
Magic Train, combine!
嘻哈合體
This was the worst combining mode I've seen.
這個合體也太差了
What's going on?
怎麼回事？
How come I'm one cart short?
怎麼少了一艘？
You're not going anywhere.
看你還怎麼跑？
Where did the last piece go?
最後一個分身到底去哪了？
What happened?
怎麼會這樣呢？
Your invention is not that good either.
你這個發明也不怎麼樣啊
How dare you laugh at my invention? I will show you!
竟敢嘲笑我的發明 我一定會讓你好看
Is Wolffy crazy?
灰太狼是不是瘋了？
Whatever. I'll just run.
不管了，趕緊逃
I made it.
成功了
This is my upgraded vacuum cleaner. You're not going anywhere!
這是我的升級版吸塵器，你跑不掉的
Dad!
爸爸！
Mom and I picked up a spaceship on the street
我跟媽媽在街上撿到了一艘
that looks exactly like the one we got at the toy store.
和玩具店一模一樣的飛船
Willie is in there! Magic Train, Combine!
原來在小灰灰那，嘻哈合體
Even if you are combined, my vacuum cleaner can suck you in.
就算合體也一樣把你吸進來
Magic Train, full power.
嘻哈號馬力全開
Paddi, I'll get you!
懶羊羊你給我等著
Paddi, remember. Don't ever abuse Magic Train again.
懶羊羊，記住了 你以後別再亂用嘻哈號了
I won't.
不敢了
Right, Weslie, I found something interesting.
對了，喜羊羊，我發現了一個新玩意
Look.
你看
Wolffy's vacuum cleaner is quite fun. It can be used for cleaning.
灰太狼的這個吸塵器還挺好玩的 可以用來打掃衛生
I think it's better not to use Wolffy's things.
我還是覺得你不要亂用 灰太狼的東西比較好啊
Ouch! Weslie, please help me.
喜羊羊，快來幫幫我
I told you not to use it.
我都跟你說不要亂用了
I won't do it ever again.
我以後再也不敢了